Thank you.
Second item is invocation by 1st.
We're messing with the church pastor, J.
I'm not breaking it.
Thanks for being here tonight.
That is part.
Hold it one together for some of us here at the city at the end of a long day already,
and so we give thanks for these who have agreed and put themselves forward to be represented
as of the whole city, and we pray your blessings upon their work and their deliberations tonight.
We do give thanks for persons who step forward, because this is not a job that pays a lot
or gives the kinds of rewards that we seek out, such as like not phone calls and complaints
and difficult conversations that don't seem to be resolved.
But you call us to be a city that works and to do the work that we need to do to be a city
that can function together cooperatively, and harmoniously we give thanks for these people
and this counsel and for the work that they try to do on all our behalf.
And we pray that they be guided by your wisdom and your compassion, and that we all be citizens that
dedicated not to our personal agendas, but to a shared community where your purposes are made real
and all that we do and say.
And your sons, then we pray.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the Friday of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God, the English of the Wolf with liberty and justice
as well.
Okay.
I was always public in person.
I'm scared to a personal therapist as anyone the audience it wishes to address, to counsel, or
excuse me, the authority on any of the agenda.
Being none of I'm fine with the consent agenda staff is recommending item 6-8, which are claims
in a couple of budget amendments for the consent agenda.
Do we have any questions on any of those?
If not, we have a motion to approve the consent agenda.
Most approved consent agenda.
Second.
Roll call please.
Johnson.
Aye.
Forster.
question.
Aye.
I'm nine as new business.
Any new business for any of the trustees or dean?
No.
Staff reports are in your packet.
Item 11 is trustee community announcements.
Any announcements?
All those are German.
Do we have a motion to adjourn?
Looks adjourned.
I'll sign it.
Roll call please.
Aye.
Forster.
Johnson.
Aye.